<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Fungi lite (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.FungiLite</packageId>
  <author>Druidefuzi</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/FungiLite</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/erdelf/AlienRaces/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Druidefuzis mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2129406860

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/FungiLite][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/6KqTKks.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
[u][b]This is the Race "Fungi" from my mod Mushrooms and Shroomans.[/b][/u]

I´m currently redrawing everything in 512x512 and i thought that it would be a good idea to release only the race without their f´ed up stuff.
Currently, they got 36 different faces. 

[b]Background (lite)[/b]
Once enslaved , mistreated , torturted and cursed with a life expectancy of 15 years, after a violent escape, the Fungi simply slowly forgot their past over thousands of years. Now they are in a tribal stage , just trying to survive.
Scientists claim that they are genetically altered humans. No one remembers what happened back then. At least in this region of the galaxy.

[b]Defining Traits[/b]
Nearly all of them are night owls
They dont mind being naked 
They can not wear hats, due to their many different heads.
They can only wear vanilla stuff, i had to forbid everything cause hats are not classified as hats and added all vanilla clothings after that.
They eat from corpses too , they don´t mind eating humanoid meat (Only cooked, they are no animals :D)
They like it hot , they have a hard time surviving cold habitats.
The Fungi are often accompanied by their beloved shroomimals.
Shroomimals can sting with their Tail , causing a flesh eating spore infection, which lets the victim endure high pain and they puke all the time. It´s a tendable Infection. If not treated, the victim will die fast.


[b]Obviously, you need Humanoid Alien Races 2.0, Big Credits to Erdelf for making other races possible.[/b]

Huge Thanks to Ogliss, he provided the code to make this race growable! You may be interested in his mods if you like warhammer. Check his mods out! 

If you want to play that race , just pick the scenario : " Oh look! Shroomies! "

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]</description>
</ModMetaData>